<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PruebaIIPuebliando409</string>
    <string name="titulohoteles">
        Go ahead and walk through the streets!
    </string>
    <string name="resenahoteles">
        If you happen to pass by La Fundadora de Pueblos, know that countryside accommodations are among the top choices.
        You can rent them by the hour, overnight,
        or for weeks, for much less than what a plan in a hotel in faraway places would cost you. Theres no need to worry about the view, a
        s the panorama of the municipality is charming...
    </string>
    <string name="botonhotel">HOTELS</string>
    <string name="titulorestaurantes">
    Feeling hungry? Look around then!
    </string>
    <string name="resenarestaurantes">
        In Copa, Antioquian food doesnt keep in low fire. Come over to Donde Aide to try a delicious full mondongo, or drive by the Santa Rosa stop and
        assemble the most paisa buffet you can imagine And of course, whether its on the highway or at any restaurant, youll have more than
        enough for that smoky-flavored mazamorra. Rest assured, where one person eats, two can eat, and theres plenty left for three in case
        the four dont have seconds.
    </string>
    <string name="botonrestaurante">RESTAURANTS</string>
    <string name="titulositios">
        Choose main park, sanctuary, main hill or the trails!
    </string>
    <string name="resenasitios">
        This is a municipality that harmoniously combines its natural wealth, such as the Piedras Blancas Park it shares with Guarne,
        and its historical value, represented by the Nuestra Señora de San Juan de la Tasajera Church,
        the place where the first Catholic Mass was officiated in the Valle de Aburrá on September 8, 1541. Located forty minutes away from Medellin,
        with good road access and many country estates for those seeking warm weather near the capital of Antioquia
    </string>
    <string name="botonsitios">Touristic sites</string>

    <string name="Opcion1">Spanish</string>
    <string name="Opcion2">English</string>
    <string name="Opcion3">Portuguese</string>
    <string name="Opcion4">About us</string>
</resources>